[theme music playing]
Don't you know that I was
using her to find out?
-Find out what?
-I know she discovered something
about your beloved Ivy!
[Fernan] Nimfa!
-Nimfa!
-Mister Fernan!
[Camia] Of all the places here
in Poblacion Ardiente,
why did they put Nimfa's body
in front of your headquarters?
[Diego] I can only think of two things.
It's either they'll have me killed,
or have me framed.
-I need to act fast.
-[cops firing shots]
[Julio] Your inheritance, the armory,
and everything in it.
We almost lost everything
because of that bastard, Diego.
[Arnaldo] If you think…
you can stop me from carrying out my plans
because of that raid, you're wrong.
Mr. Torillo, we have a warrant
for your arrest
for the murder of Nimfa Naig.
[Camia] I'm sure the Ardientes
are behind this.
They're afraid of losing the election.
That's why they're framing Diego.
[Diego] I'm going with them.
But we all know who really killed Nimfa.
It was Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo,
and I will prove it!
[Fernan] I just want someone to
pay for my daughter's death.
And if it is Diego, prison
won't be enough as punishment.
What did you do to Diego?
[Arnaldo] It was a frame-up.
And it was so easy.
-That's enough!
-I'll kill him! You bastard!
[Camia] Don't worry.
We'll look into your case,
so you won't have to stay here for long.
-It's like you have…
-Ouch!
so many secrets.
Maybe Nimfa isn't the only one you killed.
I haven't killed anyone aside from Nimfa.
And I sent Diego to jail
so I'd stop feeling jealous.
[Julio] Tonight, I will end your misery.
What do you mean?
Just prepare a beautiful black dress.
[Raul] Camia, he's my son.
I have the right
to help him get out of here.
A father who blindly
follows the Ardientes.
You won't prove anything to me or anyone
as long as you're under
the Ardientes' thumb.
-He wouldn't leave…
-Emilia.
…our side. You know why, Camia?
Because he's only mine.
[Arnaldo] Grandpa, where are you?
I'm at Raul's final resting place.
Well, you make sure you punish him good.
Oh, don't worry. I will.
Raul is all yours, Emilia.
No one's taking him from you.
Really?
You don't miss his handsome face?
What about your--
Say one more word
and I'll cut your tongue out!
-Oh, really?
-Yes!
[phone ringing]
[Raul] Emilia, stop!
-Emilia, that's enough!
-Give that back!
-Emilia, let's go!
-Oops!
-Someone's calling.
-Emilia, give that back!
-That's mine!
-Wait.
Hey! A!
A is calling. Is it…
Lily Cruz?
Wait.
Let me take it.
Hello?
Lily Cruz?
-Give that back!
-Hello, A?
-Hello?
-I said…
-There you go!
-Give that back!
Shove it down your throat!
Be thankful my husband
and my aunt were here to stop me,
or I would've pulled all your hair out!
Let's go, Emilia.
-[sighs heavily]
-Aunt Camia…
are you okay?
Yes, Diego.
Let's go, Mr. Torillo.
-Auntie.
-Diego.
-Attorney.
Come here!
Are you okay?
Yes, attorney. Thank you.
-Come here!
-You're hurting me,
-Raul!
-Why do you keep on…
following me?
This is my problem!
Mind your own business!
You're making things complicated!
So, it's my fault?!
You always think it's my fault!
Isn't it?!
You always think I'm the problem!
You know what the real problem is?
My love for you! That's the real problem.
-Your love?
-I'm still holding on
to the idea that you'll love me
back someday, Raul!
But it seems like you never will.
Papa's right.
You make me miserable, Raul!
That's not true. I did not make
your life miserable, Emilia.
Your father did!
You let him control our lives!
We could have lived
a simple life with the kids!
It could have been just you,
me, Arnaldo, and Diego!
Even when they were kids,
all they saw was greed and cruelty!
Your Papa taught them that!
That's why they turned out this way!
Especially Arnaldo! He can't
even show you some compassion!
My father and Arnaldo both love me!
Do you seriously believe
your father loves you?!
Really?
I'm the only one
who still loves you, Emilia!
-[Emilia crying]
-[Raul] Okay?
And if your father really loved you,
why didn't he ask you to run for governor?
Why'd he ask Arnaldo?
Aren't you supposed to be better?!
You're more experienced!
Love, my ass!
[Claire] Raul, that's enough.
[Emilia wailing]
I'm always…
[Emilia weeping]
-Wait, what's this about?!
-Mr. Raul, you need to come with us.
-Wait! What's going on?!
-The congressman sent us.
Wait. He's not going.
Raul, please, you have to go.
-No.
-No. Arnaldo deserved it.
Our son needed to be taught a lesson!
I'm coming too!
[tense music playing]
Papa,
you wanted to see me?
[Julio scoffs]
Such cockiness, Raul.
I like that.
And I do hope you stay that way
when I make you pay
for what you did to Arnaldo.
Well,
what you see is what you get.
Choose one here.
Which one should I use?
Maybe the good old. 45?
One bullet between your eyes…
Done.
Or…
Maybe the long arm.
I could make you suffer a little.
But, if you want…
I could use this knife!
I'll stab you until you bleed out.
[Emilia] No, please, Papa.
Don't punish Raul.
He only did that to discipline Arnaldo.
[Raul] Papa,
Arnaldo is my son.
And as his father, I have
the right to discipline my own.
He was disrespecting me and Emilia!
He doesn't even respect us as his parents!
Only I…
have the right to discipline Arnaldo.
No, Papa!
We are his parents!
It is our responsibility
to instill some discipline in Arnaldo!
Please!
Don't give me that
crappy concerned parent card!
It's not like you were
ever good parents to him!
That's because you didn't give us a chance
to become parents to him!
You took him as your own
because you never had a son!
So, what if I did? Hmm?
Look at him now!
See how successful he has become.
[Julio scoffs]
If I had trusted you two to raise him,
he'd be a vendor on the streets!
So, he's successful…
But, how'd he turn out?!
He's no different than you!
He's a criminal now!
-Kill this insolent bastard!
-Papa! Papa, don't! Don't!
-No, Papa, please!
-How brave.
Papa,
if you're going to kill Raul, kill me too.
-Please.
-What?
Please, Papa.
-Get out of the way!
-No, don't.
Emilia, just leave. Come on, let go.
Get out of here, Raul.
-Leave.
-I'm not going anywhere.
Leave!
Please leave.
You're crazy, Emilia! You are plain loco!
Someday, you will regret all of these.
I don't think so!
-Oh, yes!
-I'll enjoy it.
But I'll never regret it.
Bunch of fools!
[exhales sharply]
-Sir, Miss Ivy isn't here.
-What?!
-She's not--
-Louder! I can't hear you!
-Sir, she isn't home.
-She's out?
-Yes, sir.
-Then get out of my sight.
Where'd you go again, Ivy?
To Diego?
Lily, I'm worried about Diego.
He needs to get out of that prison
because I know the Ardientes
are plotting to get rid of him.
Diego's getting out soon, Mom.
Because I have the evidence…
that will set him free.
[Arnaldo] No.
I haven't killed anyone aside from Nimfa.
Wait, if you release this, that means…
I'll reveal my true identity.
I will tell the world that I am Lily.
-No…
-Mom.
That's the only way
I can think of to help Diego
and put a stop to Arnaldo's ruthlessness.
Lily's coming back,
so they better watch out.
Emilia?
You know, Auntie,
Raul is right.
Papa destroyed us all.
And I'm sure…
his enemies…
will stand against him.
[tense music playing]
[Natalie] Raul?
You seem so restless
ever since you came back here.
Is there a problem?
It's time to bring the Ardientes down.
Finally!
I've longed to face your wife!
What do you think I should do to her?
Shave her head?
Have her raped?
Or better yet,
should I shoot her as many times
as she shot my father?
I'm so excited!
Rufo.
Go to your boss.
Tell him I want to meet up.
We need to talk.
I'll need a lot of men.
Hold on, Diego.
I'll get you out of prison…
my son.
How did that bastard leave
without a scratch?
His time will come.
But when?
When he finally gets away?
Or when he gets Diego out of prison?
[Julio chuckling]
He does not have the power
nor the capacity to do that.
Okay, but what if Mom helps him?
Oh, Emilia.
Emilia, your mother, can be
stupid at times because of love.
But she's not stupid enough to do anything
that would ruin our family.
[Arnaldo laughing]
You don't know that.
People can really do
stupid things because of love.
Are we still talking about Emilia or…
your fiancée?
I don't know, Grandpa.
I feel Ivy is keeping
her true relationship
with Diego a secret.
Hmm…
Well,
there's only one way to find out.
Test her.
How?
Use Diego.
[tense music playing]
[cop] All right punks!
Go to sleep!
[tense music playing]
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
[grunting]
[groans]
Diego.
Diego!
-Lily…
-Diego!
Mom, they're beating Diego up.
Something bad is happening to Diego.
Lily, you're just dreaming.
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
Get him!
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
[grunts]
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
[Ivy] Mom, I don't know what I
would do if something…
happens to Diego.
-[grunts]
-[thuds]
[Camia] Lily.
Diego is safe.
He's strong.
Nothing bad will happen to him.
-[thuds]
-[grunts]
[grunting]
[action music playing]
-[screaming]
-[grunts]
[detainee groaning]
Who hired you?
Who hired you?!
The police.
Here's what you requested
last night, Mayor.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
I'm so excited to see Diego's
bruises when I visit him.
[scoffs]
Do you think Miss Aguas…
is excited too?
We'll see.
[Ivy] Please schedule a conference call…
with the engineering team.
Tell them we have something
to discuss, okay?
-Yes, Miss Aguas. Excuse me.
-Thank you. You may go.
Hello, Attorney.
[Georgina] I just heard
Arnaldo's confession.
But it'll only hold in court
if you testify against him.
Then, I'll do just that. No problem.
Like your mother said, it's too risky.
Besides, there are lots of other methods…
-to delay the case.
-So, tell me…
what other methods are, Attorney.
First, we need to look
for a new venue for the hearing.
And then, I'll pressure the current judge
to inhibit the case,
so we can look for a new judge
to preside over it.
Okay, you go do that.
Meanwhile,
I'll look for more
solid evidence that'll prove
Arnaldo killed Nimfa.
[phone ringing]
Speak of the devil.
Have a seat, Attorney.
Hon?
Hey, hon.
Where are you?
I'm sorry, hon.
I know you went to my place last night.
But I forgot to tell you I went to Manila.
I had to take care of something for work.
Anyway, don't worry.
I'm on my way back to you.
Did you miss me?
Well, yes. I missed you.
That's why we need to meet up later.
It's important.
Meet me at the office?
Okay, hon. See you.
[mockingly] Hello, hon?
I missed you!
How sweet.
Lovebirds.
Mom, Attorney, I have to go and
meet my fake, criminal fiancé.
Dear, take care of yourself, okay?
Mom, please tell Diego
we're doing everything we can
to get him out of prison.
See you, Attorney.
Mayor.
Good afternoon.
Hey.
Are you surprised?
Sorry, I forgot to mention
we were visiting
my beloved brother, Diego.
I'm honestly more worried…
about seeing my former friend
turned criminal.
I mean, what if…
What if he suddenly attacks us?
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
Just stay close to me.
Okay?
No one will hurt you
as long as I'm around.
Let's go?
[tense music playing]
-All right, leave us.
-Yes, Mayor.
Looks like you woke up
on the wrong side of the bed.
You're covered in bruises.
Did you fall off your bed?
Those men you hired to beat me up…
Aren't you going to ask about them?
They're in the hospital, by the way.
You might want to pay them a visit later.
Wow!
Nice one.
You've got guts for a prisoner.
Well, I'd rather have guts…
than be a spineless coward.
Are you calling me a coward?
Well? Is that it?
I'm no coward, Diego.
I'm no coward.
Then prove it.
Prove it!
[scoffs]
Fight me fair and square.
Fight?
You want me to fight you?
I don't have to.
I've already won, and you've already lost.
Who would vote for a criminal
like you, huh?
No one.
And I'm going to make sure
you rot here in jail.
You're never getting out.
Remember that.
Oh, by the way.
I also came…
to give you this.
Here.
I'll just leave this here, okay?
Ivy and I are inviting you…
to our engagement party.
But I know you won't make it.
You know why?
Because I'm finishing you off right here.
You. Will. Die. Here--
[Arnaldo grunting]
Oh! Diego! Diego! Stop it! Diego!
Diego, stop!
Diego, let go!
Diego!
-Hon!
-[Arnaldo panting]
Hon, are you okay?
Bring that bastard back to his cell.
-[Arnaldo coughs]
-Hon.
This isn't over.
[Georgina] That's right.
All of the allegations against my client,
Mr. Diego Torillo, are false.
Diego is an honest and decent man.
And that's how the people
of Ardiente know him too.
[Arnaldo clapping]
Nice.
If what you're saying is true,
then make sure you win the case.
We'll win the case because the allegations
against my client are based on lies.
Whoa.
Careful.
That statement's libelous.
I can file a complaint.
I am not afraid of the law.
I memorized the entire
Philippine Constitution.
And I'm telling you now,
I can prove that everything
I just said isn't libelous,
but factual and true.
And when I'm done doing that,
I'll go after you…
for the murder of Nimfa Naig.
[tense music playing]
Ivy.
You're too strong
for your own good, Attorney.
Be careful.
Someone might put you in your place.
I am immune to threats.
I eat them for breakfast,
lunch, and dinner.
And I only strive to win harder when…
someone threatens me.
[chuckles] Win?
I think it's too early for that.
Let's wait for the case to start first.
And it will.
But not in this puppet court
you have under your control.
Let's do it fair and square.
The way I see it, no matter
where we bring this case,
there will only be one outcome.
Diego killed Nimfa,
according to the evidence.
Mayor Torillo…
That's enough.
Let's put a stop to this.
This argument won't go anywhere.
That's why I'd like to propose something.
Let's do a pre-election survey.
Whoever wins there is the one
who's telling the truth.
Now, who are they going to choose?
A criminal…
or an honest politician like me?
Let them decide.
Hey.
Why did you go quiet all of a sudden?
Because we know
you'll manipulate the survey
to incriminate Diego further.
Let's go, Attorney.
Hon?
Hon.
Sorry, I had to use the restroom.
Okay.
Mayor, do you think you will win
the survey and the election?
Definitely.
Right, my future wife?
My future first lady.
Of course.
[Ivy] No one else will win
other than Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo.
He's the only one who should.
See?
Viva Ardiente!
Excuse me.
[upbeat music playing]
[clapping]
[Julio] This is perfect.
I'm sure Arnaldo's ratings will go up.
You are so right, Papa.
You know, Ivy makes Arnaldo desirable.
[chuckles]
Something you could never achieve
with your dog-faced husband, Raul.
Papa, can we please move on?
He already moved out, right?
What we need to focus on now
is the search for Lily Cruz.
Why?
Do you know where to find her?
Not yet, Papa.
But I'll make sure when I come back,
I'll have their heads with me,
so my headache can finally go away.
So, if you'll excuse me…
Those two women are going headhunting?
[scoffs]
I need more men.
And they have to be good.
I'm planning something big.
Is that all? I'll send my men…
first thing in the morning.
That's what I like about you.
You're sharp and dependable.
That's the agreement.
You supply the money,
and I supply the men.
We'll both benefit.
And we'll both flourish.
You can count on me.
So don't think twice about…
betraying me, Jaguar.
We're partners when it comes
to taking down the Ardientes.
That's why you can't have all the fun.
[tense music playing]
Gather all our men.
And round up every judge in Ardiente.
Tell them I need to talk to them.
Okay, Jaguar. I'm on it.
Thank you.
[somber music playing]
So, where is Raul, Emilia?
I don't know, Auntie.
He'll be gone for a while.
And while he's away,
I will eliminate everyone
who stands against our love.
First, Camia Cruz.
Then, that pest, Lily Cruz.
Because I know she's going to
come after me and Raul one day.
And then, Papa.
If he continues to disapprove of our love.
You're willing to do all that for Raul.
But, how about him?
What can he do for you?
Auntie,
some relationships are one-sided.
Just like Mama and Papa's.
Don't you agree?
And…
I'm making the same mistake.
But why, hmm?
Because it's the only kind of love I know,
and it's the kind of love
that makes me happy, Auntie.
[tense music playing]
He's here.
-[man] Yes, ma'am?
-[Emilia] Sit down.
I wasn't asking you
to look for Harry Potter.
Finding a lead shouldn't be this hard!
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I swear, I'll find her.
You're sorry? Well, I'm bored.
Update me, okay?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Or else…
I'll have someone finish you off.
You know what I'm capable of.
Yes, ma'am.
Now, go!
I can't believe I'm paying him that much.
What are you up to, Emilia?
Who are you looking for?
[line ringing]
Hello?
I have a project for you.
[tense music playing]
They're scared I'll win the elections.
That's why they set this whole thing up.
They framed me
for the murder of Nimfa Naig.
Why would they do that to you?
To ensure that their side will win.
Don't you know how the Ardientes operate?
They'll do everything
to hold on to their power.
Does that mean you're accepting
Mayor Arnaldo's challenge
to participate in a pre-election survey?
Yes.
Because I believe…
that even if I'm behind bars,
my supporters will remain loyal to me.
I am not going to reshape Ardiente.
You are.
If you really love our province,
you'll choose what is right.
You will choose change.
For a town where the people
hold more power
than those who govern it.
How are you going to prove
that you did not kill Nimfa Naig?
-Do you have proof?
-Thank you very much.
[Georgina] That's enough
questions for today.
Thank you.
[overlapping dialogue]
[Diego] I am not going to
reshape Ardiente.
You are.
If you really love our province,
you'll choose what is right.
You will choose change.
For a town where the people
hold more power…
I'm voting for the Ardientes.
-…than those who govern it.
-They've governed us for years,
and we're doing okay.
Why do we need change?
[woman] But our lives
aren't getting better.
They keep getting richer,
while we keep getting poorer.
[woman 2] While Mayor Arnaldo's
busy preparing for his wedding,
he won't notice the dilapidated
roads and bridges.
[man] Well, he's excited to get married.
Infrastructure projects
can wait, but his bride can't.
[man] What's this? Adobo or menudo?
Caldereta?
Keep eating. It's on me.
Great job with the press today, Diego.
Powerful statements.
And most importantly,
everything you said was true.
That's a trait
every leader should possess.
Thank you, Aunt Camia.
And they need to be handsome too!
Nanny!
Dignified…
-Uncle!
-and kind-hearted.
Hey, hey, hey. What's that?
What did they do to you?
It's nothing, Nanny.
What do you mean it's nothing?
Who did that to you? Tell me!
They're in the hospital.
They're recuperating.
You gave them a good beating?
Serves them right.
-Uncle, Nanny, have a seat.
-We brought you some food.
And your favorite, fritters.
Wow.
Good day.
[Loring] Here, we also brought…
your other favorites.
-Thank you, Nanny.
-Here.
[soft piano music playing]
Mister Fernan.
Diego.
Tell me what really happened to Nimfa.
Who killed her?
Wait for my signal.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Arnaldo clears throat]
Hon.
Does it still hurt?
No. It was nothing.
I feel better.
Uh… All the pain went away
when you vouched for me
in front of the press.
You know, we really make a good team.
Of course, hon. Just like what you said,
I am the future first lady
of this province,
that's why I need to meet your
expectations and of the people.
That's right.
But, hon, let me remind you.
I'm not meek like most other first ladies.
I'll be fierce.
I'll show everyone I can protect myself…
from anyone.
Just what I like.
Actually, you know what, you need a gun.
No, hon.
I already have my own.
But speaking of guns…
Where's the rifle I gave you as a gift?
You told me you had a gun collection.
That's why I gave you a rifle.
But I haven't seen you use it.
It's still with me.
Actually, it has a special place
in my armory.
-Armory?
-Yes. I'll show you.
-You have your own armory?
-Of course.
-I'll show you.
-[chuckles]
You'll be impressed.
The Ardientes.
They were the ones who killed Nimfa.
How did that happen?!
Mister Fernan.
Emilia used her.
This is Nimfa's cellphone.
You'll find their text message
exchanges there.
The last message she sent me
is still here.
She said…
"Dad…
I love you so much."
Mister Fernan…
don't worry.
We'll seek justice
for your daughter's death.
Wow, hon! You have so many guns!
Have you used every single one of them?
Well, most of them.
Hey. Check this out.
The one from you.
Thanks, hon.
You're taking good care of it.
Of course.
That one. I like that one, hon.
It's small and handy.
Oh, okay. Wait.
Colt Defender.
It's explosive…
and has intense firepower.
Very powerful,
just like me.
-Yes, just like you.
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
Hon,
can I have this?
Sure.
Thank you!
But wait, I'll need a license to use this,
just in case the need arises.
Okay, all the licenses are compiled here.
You don't have to worry.
That's amazing, hon.
All these are under your name? Really?
[tense music playing]
[chuckles]
-[phone ringing]
-Wait.
[phone ringing]
It must be work.
Oh, it's Grandpa. Excuse me.
Hello, Grandpa?
Hello, Arnaldo?
Grandpa, I can't hear you. Hello?
Yeah, we need to talk. Uh…
Come to my office.
Uh, okay, Grandpa.
[scoffs]
Choppy.
Ivy, I have to go to Grandpa's office.
He needs me.
-Okay, hon.
-I need to go.
-Can I stay here?
-Sure.
-I'll be back.
-Okay.
[suspenseful music playing]
[suspenseful music continues]
I spoke to the judge
who's handling your case.
And she won't inhibit the case.
She's obviously afraid of the Ardientes.
I offered protection, but she insisted.
Do you want me to talk to her, Attorney?
I know how it feels
to have your life
controlled by the Ardientes.
Maybe I could convince her
to not be afraid and fight.
That's a very good idea.
I'll go with you.
[Camia] Diego, I'm sorry
we won't be staying long.
Aunt Camia, be careful.
The Ardientes might be
watching that judge.
-Thank you.
-All right.
You know,
we have to get this survey
while this issue is still hot.
Okay. I'll take care of it, Grandpa.
[Julio] Yes, this will work in our favor.
Hon?
-Hon?
-Sorry, I overheard you.
Maybe I can help?
Hey, Ivy.
I mean…
your offer is welcome, but…
Arnaldo can handle it by himself.
Besides,
the last time you tried to help us,
it didn't…
turn out too well for us.
Congressman.
It seems like your
grandpa is saying I'm bad luck.
Hey. No! No! No! Don't get me wrong, Ivy.
You're not bad luck!
It's just…
W-what's this?
-What?
-Arnaldo can handle it!
My grandson doesn't need help.
And you have a lot of things to attend to.
More important things!
Like…
your engagement party with Arnaldo!
That's a big thing!
-That's right.
-We need to invite…
all the important people.
So you should attend to that. I mean…
Let the men handle the politics,
and let the women…
tend to the… to the kitchen!
Get it? There.
Division of labor.
Something like that.
Hmm.
You're early today, Judge De Jesus.
Yes. I'll wait for my driver here.
Sure, ma'am.
[man] Sir, where's…
-Yes, sir?
-Attorney Mallari?
He's inside. I'll take you there.
[tense music playing]
Judge De Jesus, please come with us.
Who are you? What do you want?
Judge.
You don't want to make a scene, do you?
Please come with us.
[suspenseful music playing]
[man] Get in.
Get in.
We arrived just in time
to meet with Judge De Jesus.
-What can I do for you, ma'am?
-We're here for Judge De Jesus.
Is she inside? I wanted to talk to her.
She just left.
Too bad, you just missed her.
Sir, has Judge De Jesus already left?
Yes, sir.
Haven't you seen her?
No.
Where did she go?
[ominous music playing]
Hello.
So…
Who did Emilia ask you to find?
Miss Lily Cruz.
Lily Cruz?
Has she been looking for Lily
for a while now?
No. She ordered me just recently.
But I think it's important
for her to find Lily.
Really?
Lily Cruz, huh?
Don't be afraid.
I won't hurt you.
In fact, I have something for you.
Rufo!
What is this for?
Judge De Jesus, I know you're smart.
So, you should know what that's for.
Who do you want to get acquitted?
I like you, Judge Rotico.
You're quick to catch on.
[sighs] Judge De Jesus,
I want you to dismiss
the case against Diego Torillo.
And you have to replace her, Judge Rotico.
Also…
I want you to move the hearing…
of Diego's case to another province.
Are you against the Ardientes?
Let's say I am.
And now that I have power over the law…
I will make the Ardientes suffer.
[Ivy] I'm sure the Ardientes
are behind Judge De Jesus' disappearance!
They're going to delay the hearing
to make sure the survey
is released beforehand.
Well, let's just hope
that Diego will win the survey.
That way, we have leverage
to pressure the court
to replace Judge De Jesus.
I'm certain Diego's going to win.
Sir, please answer this survey.
Here you go, sir.
[tense music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
[Pandoy] Diego Torillo for
the new Ardiente!
-Vote for Diego!
-Here you go!
Please vote for him!
Vote for Diego! Vote for Diego!
That's Diego Torillo, don't forget!
-Good day!
-He's the governor…
-of the people!
-Please vote for Diego.
[tense music playing]
WHO ARE YOU GOING TO VOTE
FOR IN THE UPCOMING ELECTION?
[no audible dialogue]
-Diego! Diego!
-Diego for the new Ardiente!
-Let's vote for Diego Torillo!
-Diego!
Diego! Diego!
-Diego! Diego!
-Diego for the new Ardiente!
[suspenseful music playing]
Thanks.
Thank you. Thanks.
Thank you.
[suspenseful music continues playing]
-[shouts] Grandpa! Mom!
-What?
Hon!
This isn't true!
Impossible! That's impossible!
That is not true! Diego beat me?!
I don't believe it! I don't believe it!
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Arnaldo…
[Julio] How did this dog…
beat you?!
Well?!
[thuds]
[tense music playing]
We Ardientes are the rightful
leaders of this town.
That is why we're going
to have Diego killed.
[detainee] Congressman's orders.
[Diego grunts and groans]
Why don't you accompany me?
[Ivy] I'm sorry. I'm not interested.
Even if it's about Lily Cruz?
[Ivy] I have a bad feeling about this.
Let's go home.
[Natalie laughing]
What's your problem, Natalie?
[Natalie] My poor father trusted you!
It's payback time, Emilia!
[theme music playing]